# Takao Momoto

### **Senior Front End Developer**

♥ Nagoya, Japan

pioneer95908@gmail.com

Phttps://github.com/hightecular95908

#### **SUMMARY**

Senior front-end developer with 7+ years of experience designing and building responsive web design and mobile apps in the financial industry. Proficient with CSS and JS Frameworks, with extensive knowledge of UX and user psychology. Notable achievements include boosting the conversion rate of an existing website by 80% with improved code and design.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Senior Front End Developer

#### **PandaBreak**

**=** 2019 - 2024

Nagoya, Japan

PandaBreak is a Sequoia-capital funded startup. Its contract management SaaS product modernizes the enterprise back-office.

- Created a custom client dashboard that reduced support tickets by 50%
- Collaborated with the UX/UI design teams to improve the website and applications, increasing conversion rates by 25%
- Daily maintenance of code, debugging issues and solving clients' problems
- Presented findings in a clear and concise manner to key decision-makers

#### Front End Developer

#### **Bouchard**

苗 2017 - 2019 👂 Nagoya,Japan

Bouchard is a residential real estate technology company launching their first app this summer. The app will allow consumers to see homes on demand via UBERlike technology. #SEEHOMESFAST

- Implemented performance tuning techniques on stored procedures and backend queries which resulted in 46% improvement in application performance
- I had the responsibility to train 4 people the front-end basics and helped them develop further
- Worked with an agile team of 12 members and provided end-to-end solutions for clients

#### Junior Front End Developer

#### **DocHub**

**=** 2016 - 2017

- Nagoya, Japan
- Created 4 application to solve problems among the society
- Ensured end-to-end process of data extraction until reporting and noted efficiency of close to 25%
- Developed my team-work skills by working in close collaboration with 6 other students

### **EDUCATION**

BachelorofScienceinComputer Science

KDU University College

**#** 2012 - 2016

### **TECH STACK**

**Develop mobile applications** 

**Design mockups and wireframes** 

**Building APIs** 

**Ruby on Rails React Native** 

Angular2 **React Redux Angular** 

Git **jQuery** 

### LANGUAGES

**English** 

Ruby

Proficient



Malay Native



## **TRAINING / COURSES**

#### International Business

University of Stellenbosch Business School, 2016

### **Entrepreneurship & Innovation**

University of California, Berkeley, 2016

#### Leadership

Duke University, 2011

Powered by CN Enhancy

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Junior Front-End Developer

#### **Slickdeals**

- Gathered requirements and assembled team of web developers and UX designers to build out new ticketing system, generating a scalable e-commerce platform that served millions of users per day
- Generated and implemented code for over 20 modules, including custom widgets and functionality to integrate third-party plug-ins for advanced analytics, data formatting, and multi-language support

### **PASSIONS**

**Competitive Gaming** 

**Professional Club Debating**